DEAR X
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, AND EVENTS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
Mom.
I'm here to see you.
THE LATE LIM SUN YE
How is it up there?
Is it any better?
I'm doing just fine.
This girl in my class
has been acting up.
She got on my nerves.
But it's fine.
I have something for you.
Want to know what it is?
Was it at the start of the semester?
I had to turn in
an assignment for art class.
I got the deadline wrong
and had to turn it in incomplete.
I went to my art teacher and said...
"Sir.
I was abused as a child.
I think my wrist is still weak.
I can't seem to finish my artwork.
I can't draw properly.
What should I do?"
I mistakenly thought
he'd give me a good grade
if I said that.
I'm not sure
if he really took pity on me
or if he saw through my lies.
He kept telling me
to see a psycholo--
Did you eat?
Hey.
About what I said last time.
There's no pressure at all.
Just vent and release what's inside.
TRUE LOVE COUNSELING CENTER
Give them a call.
He's an interesting guy.
I'll leave this here.
It's a gift.
Get some counseling over in hell
and be born again.
Who knows?
In your next life
your daughter might save you.
I won't ever live like you.
I won't die like you, either.
Watch from where you are
just how far I climb.
Then you'll feel less wronged
about how you died
and your death will carry more value.
JUNE 2007
GENERAL STORE
Ah Jin.
Get me two bottles.
Go on.
You're the little thief
who's been stealing from me, right?
Where's your mom?
Goddamn it.
Honey.
Are you taking me to an orphanage?
We'll live here from now on.
If you listen to your stepmom
and don't get in trouble
I'll let you stay here
until you grow up.
Will you really?
Hello.
Jun Seo.
Say hello.
He's your stepdad who just moved in.
Hi.
I'm Baek Ah Jin.
Hi, I'm Yoon Jun Seo.
All the assets that Jun Seo will get.
I told the darned old man
I'd manage it all
but the old fool won't listen.
There are more mouths to feed.
I won't make much
from selling this place.
Do you have any ideas?
Just you wait.
We can make a fortune with the girl.
She's worth quite a bit.
Sell a few videos of her
and we can move to a penthouse
overlooking the Hangang River.
That video you speak of.
We'll take a few
then ship her off to an orphanage.
You bet.
You'll be better off
if you don't upset her.
She has her dead mom's dirty temper.
She'll just gnaw you to bits.
I'm not some meat on the bone.
Why would she gnaw me?
EPISODE 2:
THE MOMENT A HUMAN BECOMES A DEVIL
Keep the rest.
Oh, I haven't been here in a while.
SINGWANG HIGH SCHOOL
I said no.
If people find out
you slept with my English teacher
I'll be too embarrassed
to stay in school!
Whatever.
I'm dropping out, and that's that.
Hello?
I'm looking for my daughter's school.
It must be somewhere here
but I can't tell
because I don't know where she lives.
I was thinking
of squeezing her for money.
You remember my Ah Jin, right?
- Baek Ah Jin?
- She has one pretty face.
She takes after me, Baek Seon Gyu.
It's in her blood.
Excuse me.
Did you just say
your daughter's Baek Ah Jin?
I'll call you later.
Do you know Ah Jin?
I'm her dad.
Is she better off being an orphan?
Why is she an orphan?
It's Sim Sung Hee's notebook.
SIM SUNG HEE
She noted everyone's grades,
parents' jobs, and living standards.
Everyone's graded
between A-plus and D.
Anyone below B,
she scratched out in red.
It's insane.
The kids would kill her if they knew.
BAEK AH JIN, C-MINUS
YOON JUN SEO, A-PLUS
Hey, what's an "Un..."
KIM JAE OH, D
AN UNTOUCHABLE
"Untouchable?"
What does that mean?
It sounds nasty.
Hello?
Ah Jin, your dad's here.
- Who's here?
- Your dad.
- He's here looking for you.
- Ah Jin!
At the first floor
central staircase--
Where are you off to?
Baek Ah Jin!
Where are you, Jae Oh? I'm scared.
Dad keeps calling me Satan.
Come home soon.
Ah Jin!
Baek Ah Jin!
Dad's here!
Guys, did you see Baek Ah Jin?
Her father is looking for her.
Well? You haven't seen her?
Didn't she say she was an orphan?
He's so weird. What's up with him?
Dad.
Who is this weirdo?
Dad, come with me.
Hey, Jun Seo.
You go to this school, too?
You're all grown up.
Where's Ah Jin?
Let's head out, Dad.
- Where's Ah Jin, you punk?
- I'll give you cash.
I'll give you money.
Mister!
You're not Jun Seo's dad.
Anyone who lived with me
under the same roof is my son.
- How have you been?
- Mister!
Mister!
She's psycho.
- What was that about?
- Darn it.
What's this?
- What is this?
- It looks funny.
It has your name.
What kind of bitch would...
SEO MI RI
CEO OF LONGSTAR ENTERTAINMENT
You didn't have to.
The condition is
that you never appear
near our school
or in front of Ah Jin.
Don't call even if you're dying
of a terminal illness.
She's my daughter.
A dad wants to see his daughter.
What's wrong with that?
When a dad's in a bind,
he can ask his daughter for help.
You arrogant bastard.
We can't sever our ties
just because you say so.
I thought you'd say that,
so I only got you half.
If you stay away from Ah Jin
until she graduates
I'll give you the other half.
She takes after me.
She has a pretty face.
I can get at least two large
if I sell her off to a bar.
I hope you keep your word.
Why would you go
to such lengths for her?
You're complete strangers.
You might not be related,
but you were step-siblings once.
It's so nice to see you
look out for each other.
You're pretty loyal, unlike your mom.
Is that all you have to say?
Don't you feel bad for Ah Jin at all?
What are you on about?
See you around, girlie.
Are you Baek Ah Jin?
Who are you?
I'm Seo Mi Ri
from Longstar Entertainment.
Would you like to be a celebrity?
SEO MI RI
You've heard of us, right?
I'd love to make you an actress.
No, thanks.
Sorry.
Wait.
Are you in talks with another agency?
I'd like to know
why you said no outright.
I won't do anything like that.
Where are you, Jae Oh?
Hurry up!
Dad...
Dad!
Satan.
You're scheming
so you can possess my son.
You evil devil.
- Get out of--
- Stop!
Are you crazy?
How can do this to a kid?
Dad, take it out on me instead.
Get the fuck off me.
Please stop!
You fool.
Dad, please listen to me!
- Dad!
-Leave me alone!
Jae Oh.
Dad...
Ah Jin.
Are you all right?
There's no need
to let the past get to you.
He'll stay away for a while.
He will. For a while.
Don't worry too much.
I'll do it all.
I won't ever allow
another situation...
in which I can't do anything.
Don't worry about your dad.
He'll do anything for money,
so he was easy to handle.
About Sim Sung Hee.
How did she manage
to bring your dad to our school?
Now he knows where to find you.
I took care of her.
What are you doing?
I'll give you money.
Do you think
we're after your fucking money?
What is this?
You're still all up
in other people's business.
We beat you up in middle school,
but that wasn't enough?
Why am I an untouchable?
Why ask? It means you're dirt poor.
You bitch.
This won't do.
I'll beat you to death.
You might actually get sentenced
for assault.
- What are you saying?
- You're over 14!
Shut your mouth, bitch.
I'll just kill you then kill myself.
How about that?
My family is dirt poor,
and I have no damn future anyway.
- Let's all go to prison together.
- To prison!
Yes, Auntie.
Kim Jae Oh.
You can't send your brother over
at this time of night.
The taxi fare came out to 60,000 won.
Do you know how surprised we were?
And why is he such a mess?
- I was so--
- Take him to a hospital.
He needs a guardian.
I can't be there for him.
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Auntie.
Jae Hun...
Look after him for me.
He was badly beaten
and he saw something
he shouldn't have.
He'll be in shock.
- Gosh, did your dad do something?
- I'm sorry, Auntie.
Don't forgive me.
I promise to pay...
for what I did.
Jae Oh, what on earth--
What's up?
You picked up.
I tried calling one last time.
What do you mean, "last time"?
I killed that punk.
What?
I stabbed him.
He's dead.
What you just said.
Is it true?
Was there a witness?
I'm in front of the police station.
I'm going to turn myself in.
I don't regret it, though.
Pretend to regret it.
So people will pity you.
Why?
Does the future law student think
I'll rot in prison for a long time?
Kim Jae Oh.
Even if you go to prison
you'll still be free since you've cut
the chain that was tying you down.
What's important
is what happens next.
You were a victim
before you were an assailant.
Appeal with that.
Cry, wail, and tremble,
and pretend to be remorseful.
Do you get that?
Baek Ah Jin.
You're so weird.
Thanks, though.
I don't know
if that was meant to be comforting
but thanks.
For talking in my favor
instead of criticizing me
for killing someone.
You're wrong, though.
I am trash.
I should hang up now.
Take care.
You were
the only person
who said I was useful.
Thanks for that.
Look after yourself...
Baek Ah Jin.
Sim Sung Hee did all she could
to drag down Ah Jin.
She transferred schools
in a hurry as if to flee.
As no one ever got on
Ah Jin's nerves again...
we got to enjoy
the ordinary kind of life
every other teenager did.
We lived in peace
as if God smiled upon us
and a few more seasons passed.
Ah Jin...
2018 ADMISSION RESULTS
...got into Hankook University's
Department of Law.
BAEK AH JIN, SINGWANG HIGH,
DEPARTMENT OF LAW
CONGRATULATIONS
You're in! Yes!
How did you get
into Hankook University?
DECEMBER 2017, ADMITTED
TO HANKOOK UNIVERSITY'S DEPT OF LAW
Also...
NOJEONG-DONG PATRICIDE
...the Nojeong-dong patricide
that everyone talked about
was soon forgotten.
DEFENDANT
We'll consider the jury's decision...
Will you really study law?
Once we graduate
I'll never see you again.
Why? Do you want to see me?
Then quit stealing stuff
and get your life back on track.
If and when you become
more useful than you are now
I might have a use for you.
Then we could meet again.
What Baek Ah Jin said to me that day.
Why does it come to mind today?
The defendant's parents
should've protected him, but...
Jae Oh.
You're not useless.
At least, not to me.
Will I even get another chance?
We also accept the fact
that it was an accidental death
caused during a struggle
in which the defendant protected
his brother who was being abused.
I sentence you
to three to five years in prison.
NOJEONG-DONG PATRICIDE
SENTENCED TO 3 TO 5 YEARS
I won this time.
All in.
Fuck this!
Welcome.
A pack of cigarettes.
Students can print their tuition bill
at their university's website...
4,500 won, please.
CONGRATULATIONS ON YOUR ACCEPTANCE
Baek Ah Jin, Yoon Jun Seo.
YOON JUN SEO, ANAM UNIVERSITY
You want a loan?
She's a friend of mine.
She doesn't have enough
for her tuition.
I'm in no position to help her.
So what? You know your grandpa's rich
and you want to be benevolent?
No, lend it to me.
Since I have no collateral
if you agree to give me a loan,
I'll pay you back every cent
at a higher interest rate
than what you charge your clients.
You’re using our blood ties
as collateral
but offering a higher interest
in return?
It'll be pretty steep, then.
Do you have a way to pay me back?
Yes, I'll find students to tutor
and I'm looking for a part-time job.
You'll have no time left to study.
You know I travel to Japan
every two months for treatment.
If you tag along
for three days and two nights
as my secretary and guardian
I can waive the interest. How's that?
Okay, as a debtor,
I'll pay you back with interest
and as a grandson,
I'll be your guardian.
I offered a deal,
and you're making a donation.
You're such a softie.
We leave tomorrow. Get packing.
Okay. Thank you, Grandfather.
I smell money on you.
You look nicer, too.
How did you find me?
I'm Baek Seon Gyu.
Is Jun Seo well?
What do you want?
Be nice.
Where does Ah Jin live?
Why ask me about your daughter?
That's why I asked
about your son first.
You know where she lives, don't you?
I don't.
I kept her for a few years
after you went to prison.
She left of her own accord.
You left the young girl
on the street?
I have no obligation
to look after your kid.
Jun Seo must know where she lives.
They used to be step-siblings.
Leave Jun Seo alone.
He got into Anam University.
MS BANK, BAEK AH JIN
1,577,900 WON
Did I make you wait?
- Two gukbap, please.
- Okay.
Congratulations, Ah Jin.
You got a scholarship.
What are you on about?
I applied for a scholarship for you,
and you got it just like that.
Ta-da.
My grandfather decided
to start giving scholarships
to students this year.
I raised my hand right away.
Baek Ah Jin,
you're the first recipient.
Isn't it a huge honor?
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
Did you ask your grandfather?
What did you agree to do in return?
Be a good grandson.
He regularly goes to Japan
for treatment.
He asked me to tag along this time.
I decided to be
the best grandson I can be.
Jun Seo.
Don't you think this is still...
I know what you're thinking,
but your enrollment comes first.
Let's think about the rest
when you achieve your dream.
Wait until after that. Okay?
Let's eat. This looks amazing.
Peekaboo.
Dad's here.
Get lost before I call the cops.
It's not a crime for a dad
to visit his daughter.
You want to study law
when you lack common knowledge?
Give up.
I need money.
I don't have any.
Where's the money you made
working day and night?
You must have enough for tuition.
It's not at home.
Is it in there?
It must be in here.
Hand it over.
Get away.
This bitch.
Are you crazy?
Have you lost your mind?
You're insane.
Damn it.
It's not safe to carry cash around.
Why, you...
You're crazy.
You're out of your mind.
You're insane. Totally mad.
Ah Jin.
Ah Jin?
What is it?
Is something wrong?
I'm sick.
I think I caught a cold.
Tell your mom, then.
I told her.
But she told me to sleep.
Go and lie in bed.
I'll find you some medicine.
I couldn't find the medicine.
But I'll stay with you
until you fall asleep.
Thank you, Ah Jin.
- Jun Seo.
- Yeah?
You don't look like your mom at all.
You're wrong.
Hang on.
Take a look. Don't we look alike?
Who's this man here?
That's Mr. Kang the chauffeur.
He used to drive my dad around.
He moved to another country
after Dad died.
I cried so much because he left
without saying goodbye.
Ah Jin.
I have to take Jun Seo
to see a doctor.
Will you take this to his mom
when she wakes up?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Let's go.
Jun Seo just left to see a doctor.
I'm saying
it's just you and me at home.
What do you want?
I didn't say you could come in.
Last night, Jun Seo showed me
a photo of his dad.
He must've missed him
because he didn't feel well.
But Ms. Hwang.
Jun Seo's real dad.
Why did he move abroad
without saying goodbye?
What did you just say?
Jun Seo's real dad did what?
Said who?
Did Jun Seo say so?
It's funny to see you
get serious so suddenly.
I was just joking.
Jun Seo's real dad
didn't move abroad.
Mr. Kang the chauffeur did.
Ms. Hwang.
I just figured out your secret.
Jun Seo doesn't know yet.
But what would happen
if he were to find out?
Forget about that.
What if his grandfather were to know?
Are you blackmailing me?
How dare a kid do that to an adult?
That's why
you should never dream
of sending me to an orphanage.
By the way.
I need some clothes.
This is all I brought
when I moved in.
Thanks in advance.
How does this look?
- Do I look nice?
- Yeah.
It's pretty.
What about this?
What's wrong?
Are you sulking?
I want to go outside, too.
Mom won't let me leave home.
Jun Seo.
Do you think your mom loves you?
She doesn't let you go outside
and she won't even let you
say hi to the neighbors.
Why do you think that is?
Your mom.
She's ashamed of you.
Because she doesn't love you.
Her one and only son told her
he didn't feel well
but she didn't care at all.
I'm the one who looks after you.
Ah Jin.
Does my mom
not love me?
No.
She doesn't love you.
So, she doesn't even get angry.
Your mom isn't on your side.
I bet she's thinking of ways
to get rid of us.
Baek Ah Jin, your daughter,
is absolutely psycho.
The kid manipulates me to no end.
Why cause trouble by aggravating her?
I told you to bear with it.
Forget it.
I can't live with her anymore.
Take her with you
or leave her at an orphanage.
We'll never be legally married
until then.
I'm on my way right now.
I'll text you
to bring the kid outside.
Make sure she doesn't notice.
What now?
Are you spying on me again?
I told you last time
that I'd tell Jun Seo everything
if you split us up.
You're blackmailing me again.
This is the last day
I put up with this.
He doesn't know how things are
because you keep him indoors
but I bet he has a gut feeling.
That his mom is a piece of trash.
- Stay still!
- Jun Seo!
Jun Seo!
Die.
Just die!
Die already.
Die!
Jun Seo...
Jun Seo.
Do you like your mom?
Do you think your mom loves you?
Call 911 and say
a kid fell from the second floor.
Do it right now!
What are you doing?
Ms. Hwang.
Guess what?
People don't always die
from falling from high places.
My mom didn't.
I went to check if she was dead.
But she begged me to help her
as she lay on the ground.
No.
You'll die.
- Get down from there.
- No.
I won't die easily, either.
I'm pretty lucky
and I'm a lot like my mom.
I told you she shouldn't have a scar.
How was I to know she'd jump?
I told you so many times.
She's no ordinary witch.
You can't upset her.
We can't film a girl
with a bust-up head and broken leg.
How are we to wait until she heals?
Forget the money.
Send her away already!
No way! She's worth a fortune.
You don't have to listen
to the bad things grown-ups say.
Why are you crying?
I read your diary.
DIARY
BAEK AH JIN
I also know what X means.
X gets angry
only when Jun Seo isn't around.
I'm so sad when Jun Seo isn't around.
X is such a bad grown-up.
I hope Jun Seo takes my side.
I don't want to go to an orphanage.
I can't make X angry.
Then you must know
X is a bad grown-up.
I know.
I'm sorry.
You looked after me all night.
Yet I didn't know about it.
Do you still like X?
No, I don't like her.
I only like you, Ah Jin.
You're the only nice person at home.
"Home"?
I might not be able to go back there.
I might get kicked out.
Says who?
You won't get kicked out.
I'll protect you so she can't do
anything bad to you.
Does that mean
you'll always be on my side?
Yes, I'm always on your side.
So, Ah Jin,
don't ever let go of my hand.
Okay?
Ah Jin, are you all right?
You're awake.
Do you recognize me?
How can't I
when you're holding my hand so tight?
Don't look at me like that.
I'm not dead, am I?
You were unconscious
for three days straight.
What?
What's the date today?
The enrollment deadline
was two days ago.
You didn't enroll in time,
so your admission was canceled.
We texted you many times already.
We already accepted
a student on the waiting list
so I'm sorry about your situation.
But there's nothing
we can do to help--
Ah Jin, we graduate tomorrow.
Will you be at the ceremony?
Yes, of course.
Thank you.
CONGRATULATIONS
ON YOUR GRADUATION
Ah Jin, why are you still here?
Are you all right?
I was worried when I heard
you were hospitalized.
What happened to your face?
I'm fine. I just fell.
You should've been more careful.
Congratulations on graduating.
I'll take a photo for you.
Are you ready?
One, two, three.
Smile a bit, will you?
One, two...
Jun Seo.
I'm sorry I got here so late.
Congratulations on graduating.
Let's take some photos. Let's go.
Did you hear from your grandpa?
Does he know you're graduating?
Yes.
How? Did you tell him?
Did he say anything?
About a graduation present
or something.
Like what?
I mean you're an adult now
so he might have prepared
something special--
Take this, Mom.
I'll eat with my friends.
Wait, Jun Seo. My gosh.
- Get in here.
- One, two, three.
Look here, Mom.
Thief! Catch that thief!
Oh, no!
He's a pickpocket!
You asshole!
If I hadn't cross paths
with that man then
his life would've been
completely different.
It's such a shame.
The newbie's just 20 years old?
He was sent here
from a youth detention center.
His skin is so smooth and firm.
I did, too, once.
Jeez.
What's he in for?
Murder, but not just any kind.
Patricide. My gosh.
That young guy killed his dad?
Kids these days are fearless.
I talked to him a bit,
and he's pretty docile.
He got bullied so much
at the youth detention center.
He could've stayed there
but he chose to be transferred here.
DEAR X
Subtitles by Jennifer Jean Lim